You have
to
go
through the next course
of this program I'm starting to come with.
We have more information
on the main address
and on the main address of this program.
If you have a question in
mind, please please click the?
stay right where you
are what's going on in
there you'd better start talking right now
inmate number fe40536 full name
jolene cujo this is the second time
you've caused us a problem the first
time was a failed escape attempt
and this time there's a dead
female prisoner in the crypt with a
bleeding crater in her skull I'd call
that unnatural and yet somehow you
have the balls to remain silent and
throw us attitude deadly accidents
and severe injuries seem to follow
you around like a bad fart we
can't prove you're behind them
but you can't escape that criminal
reputation of yours so from now on
you're gonna learn how to play by our
Term length pending. That's it.
Get used to this ultra security
house suit and it's your new home!
Shit shit oh shit it's a
woman a chick is here it
sure smells female doesn't
it the scent is rising
from the floor like a
thanksgiving dinner is this
the hell yeah look i threw
some shit on her face
that woman's face and my
shit touched each other
the one thing i can't
let happen is the loss of
mental strength i have to
stay strong and focused
Stress kills your stamina.
I have an objective that I have
to achieve here at this unit.
I'll get it done no matter what.
But the only way it's
going to happen is if I
don't let myself surrender
to useless exhaustion.
No.
Instead, I'll only become stronger.
If someone wished to go to
heaven, there may be a way.
Hey, don't look at me that way.
It's not like I'm telling
you to wither and die.
This heaven pertains to our spirits
and where they go after death.
As your spirit evolves,
so too does your power.
Where they ultimately end
up is what fascinates me.
I mean that place where they go.
Surely you of all people
understand what I'm talking about.
Within that place lies
real, true happiness.
If you can actually reach heaven, that is.
Though I'm aware, joy cannot be
found by having an invincible body,
vast riches, or even
reigning over all humanity.
In the end, the true winner is the
one who gets to witness heaven.
Offering whatever sacrifice.
I will go there one way or another.
I don't want to say.
Let's go!
1, 2, 3.
Come and find a way.
5, 4, 3.
I am the only one for me.
Break out, we tell me you.
I can't be able to break out.
Break out, I can't be able to break out.
The end of the world is broken.
Keep up a long time.
I can't stop waiting.
I don't stop waiting.
Don't stop waiting.
Don't stop beating them up!
Look, for example, I'll
put a sticker on this.
It splits in two.
This is my particular power.
It's called smack.
If I peel the sticker off, the pen will
revert back to its original single form,
and I can destroy it by cracking it.
I accept this power as a
revelation from the heavens.
I'll make sure you remember.
Smack is my license, my
green light for revenge.
Good morning, father.
Is it all right if I take this
beautiful flower for some reason?
I've recently come to like them.
By all means, it's yours.
Sports maximum.
Hey, FF.
Look, they're cutting you in line.
Hey, they're cutting in
front of you, I said.
Yeah, I know. Huh?
Oh, come on.
It's obvious they all look
down on me and don't accept me.
I think I just have to let it go.
Wait your turn, asshole!
That's what I would say.
Uh, that feels like a bad idea.
Huh?
You can't succeed by force.
If you want to be accepted,
you have to change. Right?
So?
I thought I should just do the
opposite of what I've been doing.
Does coffee have a reverse?
Um, tea? Oh yeah.
Let me explain what I mean.
Aatro's body wants coffee right now.
So that means I'm gonna
drink tea. Deliberately.
You get it?
I'll eat rice instead of bread.
Instead of my right hand.
I'll hold the spoon in my left and eat.
And that's how I'm gonna change myself.
By flipping everything.
Hey, check this out, FF.
These are the scars from
when I took those bullets.
They hurt like hell.
I already told you.
I just stuffed the holes with plankton.
So full recovery is up to your
own healing power. Got that?
Yeah.
Hey, Jolene, what do you
think is the opposite of pork?
I don't know, chicken or beef?
The opposite of pork is salmon.
Pigs are lazy bastards, unlike salmon.
They swim upstream like the
total badasses they are.
I like it, yeah!
But they're cutting again!
Don't let them disrespect you!
Say something!
I told you, I'm flipping
the script from before.
Like, letting more of
them cut in front of me.
Come on, keep it moving, let's go!
What the hell, guys?
Stop cutting!
We're all waiting in line here!
Hey!
Hands off, bitch!
Get back, you trash whore!
You better take a step
back, swamp monster!
Now we can slide right in!
Man, night's going, FF.
So slick!
By the way, do you know
where Ermes has been?
Haven't seen her around.
Not for days, in fact.
Wait, what?
You don't know? Huh?
Seriously? Chasing a guy?
That Hermes? For real? Yeah.
In fact, every morning recently.
You know, pretty sure it happened the day
you got those holes in your belly, too.
I can't find Jolene anywhere.
There's a panic in the courtyard.
Bad shit's going down.
Hey! Hermes!
Best to just leave her alone.
That prisoner, Hermes is after.
Yep.
You know what goes on here, right?
Mm-hmm.
I'm so happy you see fit
to rely on me, Jolene.
Cough it up, girl.
You know damn well this info
wasn't gonna come for free.
Call it a finder's fee.
Come on, I'll give you the
friends and family discount.
That's it today in the early
dawn hours a body of a woman
assumed to be collateral
damage in a gang dispute was
found in the city river a
local florida paper from six
years ago and exactly like that
quest girl said it happened?
Gloria Costello.
She's Hermes's sister.
For the past few days, I've been watching
your every move, closely and carefully,
just biding my sweet time.
Then, in a surprising turn of events,
I saw you hanging around in
the former prison cemetery,
cleaning.
You left some flowers there.
Is it the grave of some fellow gang
member that died by electric chair?
I also saw you skulking
around in the workshop,
making stuffed birds and
alligators of all things.
Had a thug like you suddenly take an
interest in crafts like taxidermy.
I mean, it doesn't really matter.
The only thing I actually give a shit
about and want to know for sure is...
Jolene and FF.
Hey, Hermes.
You're looking well.
Oh, here.
I brought you some breakfast.
By the way, that guy you've been
following around for days...
Who I'm following?
What do you mean?
Cut the crap!
His name is Sports Maximum.
Sure, outside he's a big D-gangster,
but right now he's doing a hard
time in the men's ward here.
How fascinating.
But I don't give a rat's ass.
Wait, Hermes.
If I'm not mistaken,
the reason you were sent to Green Dolphin
was for robbing a convenience store,
right?
Did you go out of your way to cause an
incident so you'd purposefully get arrested?
You wanted to get revenge on him.
As payback for your sister,
I know it. Back off.
It's against the rules
here to investigate people.
Is that right?
Sorry, but today I chose
to do the opposite thing.
It's none of your business.
Go back to your ward.
It's just as Aramis said earlier, Jolene.
You've got your own important
objective here, am I right?
I guess.
Wait for me, Gloria.
I'll get revenge on him with my own hands.
Aramis, dear.
From now on, I'll be your foster mother.
It'll be okay.
Ever since that day,
Gloria, no matter what,
you'd always put our family
first before anything else.
Hermes, we could really use your help
around this place, at least a little.
Dad's leaving us the restaurant.
I can't do this by myself.
I want us to do this together.
I don't give a shit about this place.
I'm getting out of here.
I'm gonna go to college on a
track and field scholarship.
Now butt out of my life and
stop acting like my mother.
Hermes, wait!
Where are you going?
Please, help me.
I want you to hold that chunk
of wood there in your mouth.
Not like a dog chews a bone, but
the way a baby sucks on a Bang.
She had no plans to
look around that corner,
nor would she have reported them anyway.
Leave the ones that move in
darkness to those in darkness.
Otherwise,
there's no way you could operate a
functioning restaurant in that trashy city.
But that night...
Gloria, while more than aware of the
dangers, had no choice but to report them.
In order to protect me...
But...
Defendant sports maximum.
Sentence of five years for tax
evasion and grievous bodily injury.
Only five years?
That's all he fucking gets?!
If the witness is like that,
we can't catch him by the tail.
A felony charge wouldn't stick.
He told those goons to kill her!
All the evidence has been destroyed.
Hey, you son of a bitch!
I'm not fucking finished with you!
Noose!
You piece of shiiiit!
I see your memories intact.
Works for me.
I...
Gloria would be so pleased.
Gloria!
I've been waiting...
years for this chance.
A place where I could get you alone.
And nobody will hear your screams but me.
That's the one thing I couldn't
stop thinking about this whole time.
What this ordeal must
have been like for Gloria.
Sports Maximum!
Now this is gonna be burned
into your memory forever!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
You can't keep me trapped in here!
Well, I know your prison term
ends in about a year or so.
Once you're outside, you'll
always have a bodyguard on point.
But here, you're my bitch!
Well, look at that, like a glove. No,
the rusty pipes in this prison aren't big
enough for a person to
fit comfortably inside.
But see, this does make a nice
improv coffin, don't you think?
Was that the sound of him falling down?
Hey, help me!
Just who the hell do you think you are?
Let me out of here right now, I'm serious!
You still don't know who I am?
Try harder!
Come on, now!
Use your last moments to think!
You threw glory into
the sewage, you bastard!
Because of that, Dad got
depressed and it made him sick.
I lost everything I had.
So apologize to them when you
get to hell, sports maximum!
If you can apologize with that
sphincter you call a mouth!
Oh, just so you know, I put
one more sticker on the pipe.
Consider it the last nail in your coffin.
Alright, it's totally sealed.
Now feel free to scream your lungs out.
And don't stop. You bitch!
Try calling for help.
Though I bet the only ones who'd even be
listening are just the
roaches and the rats.
Now you're in the sewer too, shithead!
Scream Sports Maximum!
Scream for me!
Those resurrecting from darkness,
Limp Viscuit, rise and come with me.
With the darkness, share the joy.
Limp Viscuit.
What?
What is that?
The fuck?
Something's happening!
What?
What the hell?
Could it be Sports Maximum?
Shit, my finger. It hurts.
This is a stand.
I don't get why I didn't
freaking see it before.
But it was definitely an
object with weight and mass.
Maybe a bird.
S-S-Sneaker!
R-R-R-Shaw!
Crap, did we kill it?
Did it get demolished?
I didn't count on that
guy becoming a stand user.
What's wrong?
You got real quiet, dick.
Speak up, rat got your tongue.
Did you get crushed in the pipe?
Do dreams come true?
Or maybe you're literally
in shit up to your
eyeballs and you ate so
much you drowned in it!
What is this thing?
Sports Maximum's still alive.
The power of this invisible thing
means that fucker's still in the pipe.
And he didn't die?
This one's even bigger. Shit!
So fast!
This power, could it possibly be the
stuffed alligator from the workshop?
The first one was the birds.
Does it mean that the corpses are moving?
Can the powers of the invisible
corpses actually shift and attack?
Damn that shit snake!
He's trying to get out of
the pipe by breaking it!
Hermes?
What the hell are you doing up there?
Yeah, Hermes.
Jolene was worried about you and...
Jolene! FF, no!
Don't come this way!
No!
No, FF!
There's an enemy, Jolene!
It's an alligator!
Demonic spirit is waiting on the floor!
Watch out!
Oh, shit, here goes my leg.
Hey, Hermes, what's going on? For real?
Is this a stand attack?
Yes, exactly.
It's sport's maximum tool.
While I was rotting in lockup,
he became a stand user.
Run now!
It's right behind you!
It's already moving to strike!
Don't ocean!
Hold on!
of some place other than here?
although you think i smile
inside and all the while
i'm wondering about my destiny.
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today!
Thank you.